

Hello, I am **Gigi Wilborn** Front End Web Developer Visual Designer/UI **Product Manager**

W www.gwharper.com **P** (678) 524-7265 **E** gwharperdesigns@gmail.com

Objective

Front End Web Developer with experience designing, developing, and deploying responsive websites. Several years of experience serving in a leadership role supervising numerous employees in a fast paced nursing environment. Superb communication and teamwork abilities. Great people skills when listening to the customer and determining their needs. Conditioned to being flexible and constantly working under pressure.

Education

Front End Web Development 2016 General Assembly, Atlanta, Ga

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, GIT, GitHub 10 week professional training experience covering a range of FEWD disciplines, practices, and tools.

Visual Design 2015

General Assembly, Atlanta, Ga

Photoshop, Responsive Webpage Design, UI, Style Guides 8 week professional training experience covering a range of VD disciplines, practices, and tools.

Emory University School of Nursing, Atlanta, Ga

Bachelors of Science in Nursing 1998-2002

4 year degree in Nursing specializing in Emergency and Trauma Nursing.

Professional Skills

Management Techniques Agile/Scrum

Adobe Creative Cloud:

Photoshop

Microsoft Office:

Word **Powerpoint**

Web Development: HTML 5 CSS 3 JavaScript jQuery Sublime/Brackets Text Keynote Skeleton GitHub/Git **Bootstrap**

Work Experience

Web Development and Design 2015-Present **Freelance**

Create website content, troubleshooting, and design. Refurbishing site according to client's instruction.

Emory Healthcare 2002-Present

Emergency/Trauma Nurse (Charge Nurse)

Management of critically ill patients. Ability to multitask with a team under pressure in life or death circumstances.

Atlanta City Detentionn Center 2010-2012

Director of Nursing

Management of 3 units (Medical, Mental Heath, and Medical Records). Management of 40 FTEs under ACA guidelines. Facilitating chart audits and day to day troubleshooting. Planning and executing numerous health fairs and staff training courses. Reorganization of all 3 units utilizing Agile (Scrum) Methodology.

Workshops

Atlanta City Detention Center 2011

Communicating Effectively Leadership Training Managing Performance for Supervisors Leadership Workshop Strategic Planning Training (7 months) The Art of Leadership Training

Emory Healthcare 2009

Charge Nurse Training Workshop

Relevant Experience

2nd Place at Hack-the-Planet Hackathon 2016

Served as Product Manager for the development of a virtual nurse recruiting marketplace named YouStaff.